Eugenics Record Office Records 1670-1964 Mss.Ms.Coll.77
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Trait Files, 1670-1964 (Box Series I: 1-65)
  - A:3532 - A:423261 (Box Series I-45)
    - Love of Reading, 1920-1931; A:4232 (Box Series I-45)
    - General Literature, 1921; A:42322 (Box Series I-45)
    - Artistic Tastes, 1920-1933; A:423261 (Box Series I-45)
  - A:4234 - A:4235 #9 (Box Series I-46)
    - Form Color Work, 1921-1936; A:4234 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1924-1929; A:4235 #1 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability [ contains photos], 1911-1922; A:4235 #2 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1913-1930; A:4235 #3 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1920; A:4235 #4 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1914-1930; A:4235 #5 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1920; A:4235 #6 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1919-1922; A:4235 #7 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1920-1926; A:4235 #8 (Box Series I-46)
    - Musical Ability, 1926-1929; A:4235 #9 (Box Series I-46)
  - A:4235 #10 - A:453 #2 (Box Series I-47)
    - Musical Ability, 1913-1932; A:4235 #10 (Box Series I-47)
    - Musical Ability, 1928-1935; A:4235 #11 (Box Series I-47)
    - Musical Ability, 1930-1936; A:4235 #12 (Box Series I-47)
    - Taste for Singing, 1933; A:42352 (Box Series I-47)
    - Ability in Playing Musical Instruments, 1911-1934; A;42355 (Box Series I-47)
    - Dancing, 1913; A:42357 (Box Series I-47)
    - Mechanical Ability, 1921, 1926; A:4236 (Box Series I-47)
    - Mechanical Genius, 1935; A:42363 (Box Series I-47)
    - Inventiveness, n.d.; A:42365 (Box Series I-47)
    - Athletics, 1910-1911; A:4237 (Box Series I-47)
    - Dramatic Taste, 1923-1932; A:4238 (Box Series I-47)
    - Home Life, 1920, 1922; A:42391 (Box Series I-47)
    - Travel vs. Home-Staying, 1927-1928; A:42395 (Box Series I-47)
    - Military Life, 1927; A:42397 (Box Series I-47)
    - Politics, 1930; A:423982 (Box Series I-47)
    - Public Speaking, 1925, 1935; A:423984 (Box Series I-47)
    - Love of Nature, 1920-1932; A:42399 (Box Series I-47)
    - Use of Tobacco, 1923-1929; A:42421 (Box Series I-47)
    - Use of Alcohol, 1922-1932; A:42422 (Box Series I-47)
    - Social Leadership, 1921; A:4245 (Box Series I-47)
    - Religion, 1910; A:4246 (Box Series I-47)
    - Sports, General, 1935; A:424905 (Box Series I-47)
    - Love of Fishing, 1934; A:42493 (Box Series I-47)
    - Egoism, 1919; A:425 (Box Series I-47)
    - Temper, 1915, 1919; A:42511 (Box Series I-47)
    - Self-Confidence vs. Lack of, 1919; A:42531 (Box Series I-47)
    - Pride, 1920, 1923; A:42541 (Box Series I-47)
    - Self Consciousness, 1923; A:42551 (Box Series I-47)
    - Sympathy (Feeling), 1925; A:42652 (Box Series I-47)
    - Locomotion, 1908-1931; A:4310 (Box Series I-47)
    - Toeing in, 1933; A:43107 (Box Series I-47)
    - General Physical Energy, 1928, 1934; A:4311 (Box Series I-47)
    - Posture [ contains photos], 1923-1924; A:43115 (Box Series I-47)
    - Dexterity vs. Unskillfulness, 1935; A:43121 (Box Series I-47)
    - Hyperkinesis, 1923, 1933; A:4321 (Box Series I-47)
    - Hypo-Activity, 1923; A:4322 (Box Series I-47)
    - Facial Expression, n.d.; A:438 (Box Series I-47)
    - Industriousness, 1919-1933; A:441 (Box Series I-47)
    - Decision, 1920; A:4422 (Box Series I-47)
    - Versatility vs. Fixity of Interest, 1933; A:4423 (Box Series I-47)
    - Thoroughness, 1925; A:4439 (Box Series I-47)
    - Management in Money Affairs, 1933; A:444 (Box Series I-47)
    - Absentmindedness, 1929; A:44622 (Box Series I-47)
    - Methodicalness, 1928; A:4465 (Box Series I-47)
    - Persistence, 1925, 1928; A:4467 (Box Series I-47)
    - Special Abilities, 1920; A:45 (Box Series I-47)
    - Business Ability, 1920-1934; A:4501 (Box Series I-47)
    - Money Making Ability, 1928; A:4502 (Box Series I-47)
    - Ability for Study, 1928; A:451 (Box Series I-47)
    - Executive Ability, 1933; A:4512 (Box Series I-47)
    - Reading, 1932, 1927; A:452 (Box Series I-47)
    - Penmanship, 1910-1923; A:453 #1 (Box Series I-47)
    - Penmanship, 1916; A:453 #2 (Box Series I-47)
  - A:453 #3 - A:4573 (Box Series I-48)
    - Penmanship, 1916; A:453 #3 (Box Series I-48)
    - Penmanship, 1916; A:453 #4 (Box Series I-48)
    - Spelling, 1919; A:454 (Box Series I-48)
    - Literary Ability, 1913-1934; A:4552 (Box Series I-48)
    - Language Ability, 1924-1933; A:4554 (Box Series I-48)
    - Oratory, 1914-1923; A:45542 (Box Series I-48)
    - Engineering, 1927; A:45572 (Box Series I-48)
    - Electrical Work, 1930; A:455721 (Box Series I-48)
    - Mechanical Trades, 1934; A:45578 (Box Series I-48)
    - Ability in Calculating, 1913-1928; A:4561 (Box Series I-48)
    - Mathematical Ability, 1907-1935; A:4562 (Box Series I-48)
    - Artistic Ability, 1913-1935; A:4563 (Box Series I-48)
    - Painting, 1913-1930; A:4565 (Box Series I-48)
    - Singing, 1910-1929; A:4566 #1 (Box Series I-48)
    - Singing, 1909-1936; A:4566 #2 (Box Series I-48)
    - Musical Composition, 1910-1929; A:4567 (Box Series I-48)
    - Manual Dexterity, 1925; A:4568 (Box Series I-48)
    - Domestic Arts, 1910; A:45685 (Box Series I-48)
    - Needlework, 1923-1924; A:456852 (Box Series I-48)
    - Mechanical Ability, 1910-1935; A:4571 (Box Series I-48)
    - Inventiveness, 1913-1921; A:4572 (Box Series I-48)
    - Professional Ability, 1934; A:4573 (Box Series I-48)
  - A:458 - A:48 #2 (Box Series I-49)
    - Administrators, n.d.; A:458 (Box Series I-49)
    - Leadership, 1920-1930; A:4581 #1 (Box Series I-49)
    - Leadership, 1927-1935; A:4581 #2 (Box Series I-49)
    - Athletic Ability, 1922-1938; A:459 (Box Series I-49)
    - Ability in Sports, 1934; A:4590 (Box Series I-49)
    - Boxing, 1930; A:45912 (Box Series I-49)
    - Rowing, 1931, 1933; A:4593 (Box Series I-49)
    - Swimming, 1926, 1928; A:4594 (Box Series I-49)
    - Tennis Players, 1927, 1930; A:45952 (Box Series I-49)
    - Golf, 1926; A:45954 (Box Series I-49)
    - Baseball Players, 1930; A:45956 (Box Series I-49)
    - Chess Players, 1925; A:4598 (Box Series I-49)
    - Temperament, 1914-1932; A:46 (Box Series I-49)
    - 1910-1914, A:461 (Box Series I-49)
    - Nervous Temperament, 1915-1935; A:4612 (Box Series I-49)
    - Placidity vs. Irascibility, 1928, 1932; A:4614 (Box Series I-49)
    - Irritability, 1919-1926; A:4615 (Box Series I-49)
    - Excitability, 1907, 1924; A:4616 (Box Series I-49)
    - Boisterousness, 1923-1924; A:4617 (Box Series I-49)
    - Gentleness vs. Violence, 1925; A:4621 (Box Series I-49)
    - Optimism, 1925, 1933; A:4622 (Box Series I-49)
    - Cheerfulness vs. Despondency, 1932-1936; A:4624 (Box Series I-49)
    - Joviality, 1920; A:4626 (Box Series I-49)
    - Good Nature, 1923, 1935; A:4628 (Box Series I-49)
    - Popularity, 1923; A:46284 (Box Series I-49)
    - Depression, 1920, 1927; A:4632 (Box Series I-49)
    - Worry, 1924, 1931; A:4634 (Box Series I-49)
    - Changing Moods, 1928, 1931; A:46361 (Box Series I-49)
    - Assertive, 1924; A:47 (Box Series I-49)
    - Independence, 1925-1935; A:4715 (Box Series I-49)
    - Determination - Firmness, 1927-1933; A:4722 (Box Series I-49)
    - Ambition, 1920-1931; A:4727 (Box Series I-49)
    - Forwardness vs. Bashfulness, 1923-1933; A:4735 (Box Series I-49)
    - Perserverance, 1923-1934; A:4747 (Box Series I-49)
    - Stubbornness, 1919-1935; A:4748 (Box Series I-49)
    - Opinionatedness vs. Diffidence, 1933; A:4749 (Box Series I-49)
    - Teasing, 1923; A:4753 (Box Series I-49)
    - Acquisitive, 1924; A:47571 (Box Series I-49)
    - Argumentativeness, 1923; A:47615 (Box Series I-49)
    - Conversationableness vs. Unconversationableness, 1927-1928; A:4762 (Box Series I-49)
    - Rapid Speech, 1925; A:47635 (Box Series I-49)
    - Anecdotal vs. Unanecdotal, 1934; A:4767 (Box Series I-49)
    - Wittiness, 1929; A:4768 (Box Series I-49)
    - Satire, 1923; A:4769 (Box Series I-49)
    - Thrift, 1919-1935; A:4791 (Box Series I-49)
    - Economy, 1923; A:4793 (Box Series I-49)
    - Altruistic Behavior, 1921-1922; A:48 #1 (Box Series I-49)
    - Altruistic Behavior, 1921-1922; A:48 #2 (Box Series I-49)
  - A:48 #3 - A:5526 #5 (Box Series I-50)
    - Altruistic Behavior, 1922; A:48 #3 (Box Series I-50)
    - Sensitiveness vs. Insensitiveness, 1931; A:4822 (Box Series I-50)
    - Reticence, 1923-1934; A:4835 (Box Series I-50)
    - Unselfishness, 1925, 1936; A:4845 (Box Series I-50)
    - Altruism vs. Self-Centeredness, 1934; A:4846 (Box Series I-50)
    - Philanthrophy, 1910, 1926; A:4851 (Box Series I-50)
    - Generosity, 1924-1935; A:4852 (Box Series I-50)
    - Impatience, 1920; A:4862 (Box Series I-50)
    - Capacity for Friendship, 1925; A:49011 (Box Series I-50)
    - Sociableness vs. Unsociableness, 1933; A:4911 (Box Series I-50)
    - Solitariness, 1931; A:4912 (Box Series I-50)
    - Geniality vs. Ungeniality, 1933; A:4913 (Box Series I-50)
    - Quarrelsomeness, 1921; A:49134 (Box Series I-50)
    - Diplomacy, 1925; A:4914 (Box Series I-50)
    - Organizing Ability, 1929; A:4917 (Box Series I-50)
    - Immorality, 1932; A:492 (Box Series I-50)
    - Conscientiousness, 1920, 1923; A:4921 (Box Series I-50)
    - Religiousness, 1911-1934; A:4927 (Box Series I-50)
    - Behavior in Sex Realm, n.d.; A:494 (Box Series I-50)
    - Hearing by Touch - Seeing by Smell, 1921-1924; A:51 (Box Series I-50)
    - Taste - Idiosyncracies, 1923; A:525 (Box Series I-50)
    - Absence of Sense of Smell, 1920; A:544 (Box Series I-50)
    - Hypersensitive to Odors, 1919; A:5441 (Box Series I-50)
    - Deaf Mutism, 1853-1936; A:5524 (Box Series I-50)
    - Tone Deaf, 1914-1925; A:5525 (Box Series I-50)
    - Otosclerosis, 1905-1935; A:5526 #1 (Box Series I-50)
    - Otosclerosis, 1934; A:5526 #2 (Box Series I-50)
    - Otosclerosis, 1934; A:5526 #3 (Box Series I-50)
    - Otosclerosis, 1934; A:5526 #4 (Box Series I-50)
    - Otosclerosis, 1934; A:5526 #5 (Box Series I-50)
  - A:5526 #6 - A:5526 #16 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Legends, 1934; A:5526 #6 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Tables and Working Notes, 1934; A:5526 #7 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - General, 1914-1928; A:5526 #8 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (Unanswered), 1931; A:5526 #9 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (A-D) - Families Studied, 1929; A:5526 #10 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (E-K) - Families Studied, 1928-1931; A:5526 #11 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (L-M) - Families Studied, 1928-1931; A:5526 #12 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (M-W) - Families Studied, 1913-1929; A:5526 #13 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (A-J) - Families Not Studied, 1929-1931; A:5526 #14 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (K-N) - Families Not Studied, 1928-1931; A:5526 #15 (Box Series I-51)
    - Otosclerosis - Correspondence (P-W) - Families Not Studied, 1928-1931; A:5526 #16 (Box Series I-51)
  - A:5527 - A:5615 #5 (Box Series I-52)
    - Otitis, 1903; A:5527 (Box Series I-52)
    - Cattarhal Deafness, 1930, 1935; A:5528 (Box Series I-52)
    - Meniere's Disease, 1903; A:553 (Box Series I-52)
    - Masoiditis, 1926; A:554 (Box Series I-52)
    - Other Diseases of the Ear, 1926, 1933; A:559 (Box Series I-52)
    - Tumors - Ear, 1920; A:5592 (Box Series I-52)
    - Eye, 1898-1930; A:56 (Box Series I-52)
    - Eye Diseases, 1878-1934; A:560 (Box Series I-52)
    - General Strength of Vision, 1909-1927; A:5601 (Box Series I-52)
    - Blindness, 1908-1924; A:5602 (Box Series I-52)
    - Word Blindness, 1907-1927; A:56021 (Box Series I-52)
    - Anophthalmos, 1919-1924; A:56023 (Box Series I-52)
    - Congenital Amblyopia, 1924; A:56031 (Box Series I-52)
    - Early Imperfections of Sight, 1928-1936; A:5604 (Box Series I-52)
    - Eyeball, 1927; A:561 (Box Series I-52)
    - Dropsy - Eye, n.d.; A:56102 (Box Series I-52)
    - Deep-Set Eyes, 1920-1933; A:561071 (Box Series I-52)
    - Microphthalmus, 1913-1922; A:5611 (Box Series I-52)
    - Cryptophthalmia, 1910, 1921; A:56113 (Box Series I-52)
    - Eyes of Different Size, 1919, 1924; A:5612 (Box Series I-52)
    - Glaucoma, 1855-1939; A:5613 (Box Series I-52)
    - Myopia, 1930; A:5615 #1 (Box Series I-52)
    - Myopia, 1930; A:5615 #2 (Box Series I-52)
    - Myopia, 1898-1931; A:5615 #3 (Box Series I-52)
    - Myopia, 1885-1926; A:5615 #4 (Box Series I-52)
    - Myopia, 1915-1934; A:5615 #5 (Box Series I-52)
  - A:5616 - A:5632 #3 (Box Series I-53)
    - Hyperopia, 1914-1931; A:5616 (Box Series I-53)
    - Astigmatism, 1909-1928; A:5618 (Box Series I-53)
    - Coloboma, 1894-1935; A:5619 (Box Series I-53)
    - Lens, 1926, 1928; A:562 (Box Series I-53)
    - Cataract, 1908-1931; A:5622 (Box Series I-53)
    - Cataract, Presenile, 1911-1925; A:56221 (Box Series I-53)
    - Cataract, Congenital, 1905-1916; A:56222 #1 (Box Series I-53)
    - Cataract, Congenital, 1900-1932; A:56222 #2 (Box Series I-53)
    - Cataract, Congenital, 1914-1928; A:56222 #3 (Box Series I-53)
    - Ectopia Lentis, 1879-1934; A:5624 (Box Series I-53)
    - Iris, 1911-1925; A:563 (Box Series I-53)
    - Dissimilar Eyes, 1907-1940; A:5630 (Box Series I-53)
    - Aniridia, 1915-1937; A:56312 (Box Series I-53)
    - Eye Color, 1835-1923; A:5632 #1 (Box Series I-53)
    - Eye Color, 1934; A:5632 #2 (Box Series I-53)
    - Eye Color, 1934; A:5632 #3 (Box Series I-53)
  - A:5632 #4 - A:56328 (Box Series I-54)
    - Eye Color--Training Class Study, 1911-1914; A:5632 #4 (Box Series I-54)
    - Eye Color, 1912-1928; A:5632 #5 (Box Series I-54)
    - Eye Color, 1928, 1930; A:5632 #6 (Box Series I-54)
    - Eye Color, 1908-1932; A:5632 #7 (Box Series I-54)
    - Blue Eyes, 1915; A:56321 #1 (Box Series I-54)
    - Blue Eyes, 1919-1924; A:56321 #2 (Box Series I-54)
    - Blue Eyes, 1924-1932; A:56321 #3 (Box Series I-54)
    - Brown Eyes, 1914-1929; A:56323 #1 (Box Series I-54)
    - Brown Eyes, 1920-1934; A:56323 #2 (Box Series I-54)
    - Black Eyes, 1919; A:56324 (Box Series I-54)
    - Hazel Eyes, 1923-1932; A:56325 (Box Series I-54)
    - Blue Eyes - Brown Hair, 1919-1935; A:56327 (Box Series I-54)
    - Blue Eyes - Light Hair, 1920; A:56328 (Box Series I-54)
  - A:5633 - A:5644 #3 (Box Series I-55)
    - Diseases of Eye, 1911, 1922; A:5633 (Box Series I-55)
    - Cornea, 1909-1925; A:5634 (Box Series I-55)
    - Disease of the Cornea, 1924; A:563421 (Box Series I-55)
    - Keratitis, 1912, 1919; A:563422 (Box Series I-55)
    - Parenchymatous Keratitis, 1931; A:563423 (Box Series I-55)
    - Corneal Opacity, 1914-1933; A:563425 (Box Series I-55)
    - Degeneracy of Cornea, 1915-1932; A:56345 (Box Series I-55)
    - Megalocornea, 1914-1921; A:56347 (Box Series I-55)
    - Conjunctivitis, 1930; A:56352 (Box Series I-55)
    - Pterygion, 1914; A:56354 (Box Series I-55)
    - Blue Sclerotics, 1910-1924; A:56362 (Box Series I-55)
    - Retina, 1911, 1928; A:564 (Box Series I-55)
    - Macula Lutea, 1905-1923; A:56401 (Box Series I-55)
    - Photophobia, 1911; A:56402 (Box Series I-55)
    - Choroid Coat and Disease, 1912-1927; A:5641 (Box Series I-55)
    - Choriditis, 1910-1926; A:56413 (Box Series I-55)
    - Atrophy of Optic Nerve, 1908-1932; A:5642 #1 (Box Series I-55)
    - Atrophy of Optic Nerve, 1864-1927; A:5642 #2 (Box Series I-55)
    - Atrophy of Optic Nerve, 1915-1922; A:5642 #3 (Box Series I-55)
    - Retro-Bulbar Neuritis, 1922; A:56422 (Box Series I-55)
    - Hereditary Degeneration of the Macula, 1920-1935; A:5643 (Box Series I-55)
    - Detachment of Retina, 1921; A:5645 (Box Series I-55)
    - Night-Blindness, 1919; A:5646 (Box Series I-55)
    - Retinitis Pigmentosa, 1912-1923; A:5644 #1 (Box Series I-55)
    - Retinitis Pigmentosa, 1915; A:5644 #2 (Box Series I-55)
    - Retinitis Pigmentosa, 1914-1915; A:5644 #3 (Box Series I-55)
  - A:5648 #1 - A:60 (Box Series I-56)
    - Color Blindness, 1912-1934; A:5648 #1 (Box Series I-56)
    - Color Blindness, 1844-1924; A:5648 #2 (Box Series I-56)
    - Eye Diseases and Defects, 1920-1925; A:5649 #1 (Box Series I-56)
    - Eye Diseases and Defects, 1925-1926; A:5649 #2 (Box Series I-56)
    - Eye Diseases and Defects, 1909-1934; A:5649 #3 (Box Series I-56)
    - Hemianopsia, 1926; A:56492 (Box Series I-56)
    - Glioma, 1910-1922; A:564932 (Box Series I-56)
    - Nystagmus, 1911-1929; A:5652 #1 (Box Series I-56)
    - Nystagmus, 1902-1925; A:5652 #2 (Box Series I-56)
    - Eye Muscles, Paralysis of, 1905-1924; A:5654 (Box Series I-56)
    - Strabismus, 1903-1935; A:5656 (Box Series I-56)
    - Squint, 1888-1934; A:5658 (Box Series I-56)
    - Lagophthalmus, 1915; A:57122 (Box Series I-56)
    - Ptosis, 1892-1935; A:57123 (Box Series I-56)
    - Defects of Eyelids, 1918-1927; A:5718 (Box Series I-56)
    - Deficiency of Cilia, 1912; A:574 (Box Series I-56)
    - Polytrichia, 1924; A:5745 (Box Series I-56)
    - Epicanthus [ contains photos], 1919, 1922; A:576 (Box Series I-56)
    - Sacs Under Eyes, 1921; A:577 (Box Series I-56)
    - Metabolism, 1918-1922; A:60 (Box Series I-56)
  - A:601 - A:6599 (Box Series I-57)
    - Growth, 1905-1927; A:601 (Box Series I-57)
    - Metabolism, 1932; A:602 (Box Series I-57)
    - Malnutrition, 1919; A:6092 (Box Series I-57)
    - Polydipsia, n.d.; A:6093 (Box Series I-57)
    - Teeth, 1916-1931; A:61 (Box Series I-57)
    - Teeth - Early Loss, 1923, 1927; A:6101 (Box Series I-57)
    - Teeth - Long-Lived, 1923-1924; A:6102 (Box Series I-57)
    - Poor Teeth, 1934; A:6104 (Box Series I-57)
    - Absence of 2nd Dentition, 1920; A:611 (Box Series I-57)
    - Supernumerary Teeth, 1913-1924; A:612 (Box Series I-57)
    - Third Dentition, 1910, 1919; A:613 (Box Series I-57)
    - First Dentition Accelerated, 1919; A:6141 (Box Series I-57)
    - Absence of Teeth, 1883-1924; A:615 (Box Series I-57)
    - Absence of Incisors, 1919-1927; A:6154 (Box Series I-57)
    - Teeth Abnormal Size, 1919; A:616 (Box Series I-57)
    - Double Teeth, 1930; A:6161 (Box Series I-57)
    - Protruding Teeth, 1933-1934; A:6162 (Box Series I-57)
    - Crowding of Teeth, 1914, 1919; A:6165 (Box Series I-57)
    - Crooked Teeth, 1920-1935; A:6166 (Box Series I-57)
    - Teeth - Widely Separated, 1920, 1924; A:6167 (Box Series I-57)
    - Malocclusion, 1916-1917; A:6168 (Box Series I-57)
    - Abnormal Tooth Structure, 1889-1907; A:617 (Box Series I-57)
    - Black Teeth, n.d.; A:61724 (Box Series I-57)
    - Hard Dentine, 1923; A:61741 (Box Series I-57)
    - Soft Dentine, 1913-1920; A:61742 (Box Series I-57)
    - Hypertrophy of Gums, 1931; A:6183 (Box Series I-57)
    - Pyorrhea, 1926; A:6184 (Box Series I-57)
    - Mouth, 1919-1928; A:62 (Box Series I-57)
    - Glands of Mouth, 1920, 1924; A:6203 (Box Series I-57)
    - Jaw, 1921; A:621 (Box Series I-57)
    - Cleft Palate, 1911-1952; A:6228 (Box Series I-57)
    - Cleft Palate and Hare Lip [ contains photos], 1914-1924; A:6228, 6238 #1 (Box Series I-57)
    - Cleft Palate and Hare Lip [ contains photos], 1920; A:6228, 6238 #2 (Box Series I-57)
    - Lips, 1919-1931; A:623 (Box Series I-57)
    - Hapsburg Lip, 1919; A:6233 (Box Series I-57)
    - Hare Lip, 1868-1936; A:6238 (Box Series I-57)
    - Tongue (Chewing), 1914, 1935; A:625 (Box Series I-57)
    - Pharynx, 1910; A:626 (Box Series I-57)
    - Tonsils, 1920-1921; A:6264 (Box Series I-57)
    - Quinsy, 1921; A:62641 (Box Series I-57)
    - Throat Trouble, 1928; A:6265 (Box Series I-57)
    - Adenoids; Adenectomy, n.d.; A:6266 and 62662 (Box Series I-57)
    - Congenital Malformation - Oesophagus, 1923; A:632 (Box Series I-57)
    - Swallowing Reflex, 1925; A:6361 (Box Series I-57)
    - Stomach, 1931; A:65 (Box Series I-57)
    - Stomach Trouble, 1915; A:650 (Box Series I-57)
    - Pyloric Stenosis, 1924-1933; A:6511 (Box Series I-57)
    - Acute Indigestion, 1925, 1930; A:654 (Box Series I-57)
    - Heartburn, 1924; A:6541 (Box Series I-57)
    - Ulceration of Stomach, 1907-1934; A:655 (Box Series I-57)
    - Other Defects of the Stomach, 1932; A:659 (Box Series I-57)
    - Abdominal Secretions, 1920; A:6594 (Box Series I-57)
    - Gastro-Intestinal Trouble, 1934; A:6599 (Box Series I-57)
  - A:8102 #2 (Box Series I-58)
    - Obstipation, 1926; A:6601 (Box Series I-58)
    - Diarrhoea - Infantile, n.d.; A:662 (Box Series I-58)
    - Dysentery, n.d.; A:664 (Box Series I-58)
    - Intestinal Ulcer, 1921-1933; A:6652 (Box Series I-58)
    - Megacolon, 1920-1921; A:6656 (Box Series I-58)
    - Appendicitis, 1895-1928; A:666 (Box Series I-58)
    - Appendectomy, A:6662 (Box Series I-58)
    - Other Diseases, 1927; A:6668 (Box Series I-58)
    - Other Defects, n.d.; A:6669 (Box Series I-58)
    - Diverticulum, 1926; A:667 (Box Series I-58)
    - Liver and Gall Bladder, A:67 (Box Series I-58)
    - Cirrhosis, 1916-1930; A:672 (Box Series I-58)
    - Biliary Calculi--Gall Stones, 1933; A:676 (Box Series I-58)
    - Jaundice, 1908-1935; A:6772 (Box Series I-58)
    - Diseases of the Liver, 1931; A:678 (Box Series I-58)
    - Rectum, n.d.; A:68 (Box Series I-58)
    - Polypus Rectum, 1914; A:6814 (Box Series I-58)
    - Fistula in Ano, n.d.; A:683 (Box Series I-58)
    - Other Diseases, 1925; A:688 (Box Series I-58)
    - Absence of Anus, n.d.; A:6891 (Box Series I-58)
    - Respiratory System, 1924; A:7 (Box Series I-58)
    - Colds, 1919, 1930; A:712 (Box Series I-58)
    - Catarrh, 1923; A:713 (Box Series I-58)
    - Hay Fever, 1915-1934; A:717 (Box Series I-58)
    - Epistaxis, 1865-1940; A:718 (Box Series I-58)
    - Other Diseases and Defects, 1916; A:719 (Box Series I-58)
    - Sinusitis, 1928; A:7191 (Box Series I-58)
    - Aerocele--Open Gillslits, 1934; A:722 (Box Series I-58)
    - Vocal Chords, 1923; A:725 (Box Series I-58)
    - Lung, n.d.; A:73 (Box Series I-58)
    - Pulmonary Hemmorhage, 1923; A:731 (Box Series I-58)
    - Pneumonia, 1920, 1926; A:734 (Box Series I-58)
    - Trachea and Bronchus, 1928; A:74 (Box Series I-58)
    - Bronchial Fistula, n.d.; A:741 (Box Series I-58)
    - Bronchitis, 1919; A:742 (Box Series I-58)
    - Bronchitis, Chronic, n.d.; A:744 (Box Series I-58)
    - Asthma, 1909-1933; A:746 (Box Series I-58)
    - Pleural Effusion, n.d.; A:751 (Box Series I-58)
    - Circulatory System, 1925; A:8 (Box Series I-58)
    - Circulatory System (General), 1925, 1932; A:80 (Box Series I-58)
    - Congenital Malformations of Heart, 1901; A:802 (Box Series I-58)
    - Heart Disease, 1910-1927; A:804 (Box Series I-58)
    - Blood, 1914-1932; A:81 (Box Series I-58)
    - Hyperglobulie, 1917-1925; A:8101 (Box Series I-58)
    - Hemophilia, 1906-1934; A:8102 #1 (Box Series I-58)
    - Hemophilia, 1834-1935; A:8102 #2 (Box Series I-58)
  - A:81022 - A:884 #3 (Box Series I-59)
    - Hemorrhagic Diathesis, 1918-1934; A:81022 (Box Series I-59)
    - Pseudo Haemophilia, 1926-1927; A:81024 (Box Series I-59)
    - Blood Grouping, 1921-1931; A:81025 (Box Series I-59)
    - Eosinophilia, 1931, 1933; A:81031 (Box Series I-59)
    - Blood Agglutinization, 1910, 1923; A:81041 (Box Series I-59)
    - Cholaemia, 1909-1914; A:8107 (Box Series I-59)
    - Abnormal Elements in Blood, 1923-1935; A:811 (Box Series I-59)
    - Heart, 1924, 1929; A:82 (Box Series I-59)
    - Congenital Malformation of the Heart, 1926, 1929; A:8211 (Box Series I-59)
    - Abnormal Position of Heart, 1926; A:82111 (Box Series I-59)
    - Abnormal Heart Beat, 1921, 1925; A:82112 (Box Series I-59)
    - Dropsy, Heart, 1910; A:8215 (Box Series I-59)
    - Endocarditis, Chronic, 1926; A:822 (Box Series I-59)
    - Other Diseases and Defects, 1920, 1923; A:824 (Box Series I-59)
    - Arteries, n.d.; A:83 (Box Series I-59)
    - Capillary Defect, 1923, 1925; A:8305 (Box Series I-59)
    - Angioma, 1926-1934; A:8312 (Box Series I-59)
    - Blushing, 1924; A:83142 (Box Series I-59)
    - Elephantiasis, 1913, 1923; A:8315 (Box Series I-59)
    - Aneurysm of the Blood Vessels, 1935; A:832 (Box Series I-59)
    - Arteriosclerosis, 1912-1923; A:834 (Box Series I-59)